You think you can fix me?
你觉得你能让我变成正常人
Jean, you are not broken.
Jean   你没有不正常
The mind is a fragile thing. It takes only the slightest tap to tip it in the wrong direction.
心灵是脆弱的   只需要轻轻一点就可以把它往错误的方向引
Charles, what did you do?
Charles 你做了什么
I had to keep her stable. I protected her.
我必须保持她的稳定   我保护了她
From the truth?
以免她知道真相
There's another word for that.
有另一个词表达这个意思
I came looking for answers.
我们来寻找答案
You feel like you don't belong here.
你觉得自己不属于这里
You don't.
你就是不属于这里
They can't begin to comprehend what you are.
他们无法开始理解你
She's changing.
她正在变
Into what?
变成什么
You didn't come here looking for answers.
你来这里不是为了寻找答案
You came here looking for permission.
你来这里是为了寻求许可
Jean.
Jean